So we're gonna go to the crawler now,
we'll go to the glucan console.
Uh, scroll down. We go to crawlers.
And then we already have the crawler, right?
We already have the crawler, the original one.
We'll click on that. We'll actually choose that.
And then action duplicate crawler.
And this time we're gonna be providing the path of
the aggregated layer.
So we'll just edit this. And here's a path aggregated.
We'll just copy this entire path.
In fact, we'll go back and, uh, paste it right here.
We'll scroll down, update the source, and then go to next.
Um, then next, this time we'll name these as, um,
aggregated, A GG in fact, underscore.
That should be good enough. And, uh, we'll do a next,
we'll come down and create color.
Okay, it says the copy of the, we just named it.
We already had a previous one, in fact. Copy.
We'll add this to IAGG. There you go.
And then next, next, we'll do a next
and then finally create crawler.
The crawler is already, we're gonna just run it now
and we'll wait for it to finish.
Okay, you refresh it. It's already running here. In fact.